{
"mainView": [
             {
             "categoryName": "Question and answer",
             "categoryImage": "apple"
             },
             {
             "categoryName": "Guessing Images",
             "categoryImage": "swiftLogo"
             }
    ],
    
"questionList": [ 
    {
        "index": "-1-",
        "question": "Billy’s mother had five children. The first was named Lala, the second was named Lele, the third was named Lili, the fourth was named Lolo. What was the fifth child named?",
        "answer": "Billy"
    },
    {
        "index": "-2-",
        "question": "Choose the correct sentence: “the yolk of the egg is white” or “the yolk of the egg is white.”,first or second?",
        "answer": "Neither"
    },
    {
        "index": "-3-",
        "question": "It’s as light as a feather, but the strongest person can’t hold it for more than five minutes. What is it?",
        "answer": "Breath"
    },
    {
        "index": "-4-",
        "question": "The more there is, the less you see. What is it?",
        "answer": "Fog"
    },
    {
        "index": "-5-",
        "question": "What gets more wet while it dries?",
        "answer": "Towel"
    },
    {
        "index": "-6-",
        "question": "You can find it in Mercury, Earth, Mars, Jupiter and Saturn, but not in Venus or Neptune. What is it?",
        "answer" : "R"
    },
    {
        "index": "-7-",
        "question": "It likes food, but water kills it. What is it?",
        "answer": "Fire"
    },
    {
        "index": "-8-",
        "question": " What’s full of holes but can still hold water?",
        "answer": "Sponge"
    },
    {
        "index": "-9-",
        "question": "Which is heavier, a pound of feathers or a pound of rocks?",
        "answer": "Neither"
    },
    {
        "index": "-10-",
        "question": "There are three houses. One is red, one is blue and one is white. If the red house is to the left of the house in the middle, and the blue house is to the right of the house in the middle, where’s the white house?",
        "answer": "In Washington, D.C."
    },
    {
        "index": "-11-",
        "question": "It’s at the center of gravity and you can find it in Venus, but not Mars. What is it?",
        "answer": "V"
    },
    {
        "index": "-12-",
        "question": "What travels faster: heat or cold?",
        "answer": "Heat travels faster because you can catch a cold!"
    },
    {
        "index": "-13-",
        "question": "A man was walking in the rain in the middle of nowhere without a coat or an umbrella. He got soaked, but not a single hair on his head was wet. How can this be?",
        "answer": "He was bald."
    },
    {
        "index": "-14-",
        "question": "A cowboy rode into town on Friday. He stayed in town for three days and rode back out on Friday. How is this possible?",
        "answer": "The horse’s name was Friday."
    }
    ],
    
"guessImages" : [
    {
        "index":"-1-"
    },
    {
        "index":"-2-"
    },
    {
        "index":"-3-"
    },
    {
        "index":"-4-"
    },
    {
        "index":"-5-"
    },
    {
        "index":"-6-"
    }
    ]
}